(Episode 3)
Hey! Stop right there.
Give me my money back.
Leave the money.
If you run away now,
don't bother about coming back.
You are a bad son.
Why are you bringing water
when it's raining?
Well, Mo...
The water will be shut off today.
Give it to me. I will do it.
Do you want me to do the cleaning? Mo...
Stop bothering me.
I will ask you when I need it.
If you can't call me Mom,
just call me Ma'am.
Soon Im.
- Yes?
- There is a call for you.
Why did you give her my phone number?
Hello.
Let's go in.
Where is your mom?
She went for an errand.
Is that so? Can you make soup?
Yes, I can. Please wait for a moment.
Give her back to you?
I am sorry.
Please give Eun Seo back to me.
Go back, please.
Please let me meet Eun Seo.
Please let me meet my Eun Seo.
Do I owe you something?
Is she the debt I owe you?
Then give me my Sin Ae back.
I cannot send Sin Ae to your home.
Why is that?
She...
does not want to come back here ever.
Did she say that?
We are leaving for the U.S. soon.
I cannot leave Eun Seo behind.
Is Sin Ae leaving with you?
I am sorry.
I know we are being selfish, but,
can't we take care of...
both Sin Ae and Eun Seo?
I do not mean to keep her forever
as my daughter.
Only until she graduates
from university...
or only while we are in the U.S...
I will take good care of them. Please?
Do you think Eun Seo...
can even attend university here?
She might end up
working at your restaurant.
Please do not be greedy.
Greedy?
What I mean is, we can offer them more.
Look.
You are right.
I am being greedy.
That is why I make Eun Seo
work at the restaurant.
And I use her for my sake.
You have no idea how much work
is needed at the restaurant.
It gets much busier in winter.
So how can I give her to you?
The daughter I have raised until now
does not even want to come back here.
What more can I say?
Ms. Soon Im.
How much is this?
For now,
we would like to express our gratitude
for raising Sin Ae so far.
Eun Seo.
If you give me Eun Seo,
we will do our best...
Can you give me everything you have?
What?
Can you?
Is this the value of Sin Ae and Eun Seo?
Are you trying to haggle
with our daughters for money?
Ms. Soon Im.
Do all rich people do it this way?
How dare you offer me this dirty money?
Come here.
Okay.
This soup has no meat, just bones.
Right, there is nothing but bones.
There are only bones.
So, you must sing a song for us.
Can you sing?
I bet she can sing just like her mother.
Okay, go ahead.
I am in a good mood, so...
Sing for us.
Are you not going to sing?
All right.
Then, fill up my glass. Come here.
Yes, fill up my glass.
Fill up my glass now.
Come on.
I said, fill up my glass.
Come on, fill up my glass.
- Soon Im.
- Come with me.
Soon Im, what are you doing?
Do not kill the mood.
Mom.
Eun Seo.
She called you "Mom."
If she doesn't feel it from her heart,
she doesn't call anyone "Mom."
She has never called me...
Mom, not even once.
You were right about things.
If she stays with me,
she would have a tough life...
working at the restaurant.
She won't be able to do what she wants.
She won't be able to study
as much as she wants.
She won't have a decent life.
All right.
I can live as if I never had a child.
Honestly, raising a child
is a burden for me.
Yes,
I don't deserve to be a mom.
Take her with you.
Your family is leaving for the U.S.
You should go with them.
Take her with you.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Eun Seo.
Eun Seo, I...
Let's go home, Eun Seo.
I can't go with you.
I'm not your daughter.
You have Sin Ae and Jun Seo.
No, Eun Seo.
I am all right.
I am fine, Mom.
So, don't worry about me.
Eun Seo.
Eun Seo. No.
Mom.
Mom, I am sorry.
I am sorry, mom.
Don't send me away.
Eun Seo.
Let me have a bite.
Eun Seo, come join us here.
We are fine. We will have lunch here.
Eun Seo, let's eat.
Eun Seo, what is this?
That is head meat, pig's head.
Thanks for the meal.
It is tasty.
I will have more.
Eun Seo, slow it down.
I'll stop following you.
Do you know this road leads to the beach?
Really?
How many days are left
until your birthday?
Would you like to go to the beach
on your birthday?
What I regret the most is that...
I left behind the watch
you had given me...
for my birthday last year, at home.
That was the first birthday gift
you had ever given me.
Was it the first time?
Yes, it was.
How stingy you are.
You had a total of 14 opportunities.
You are a fool.
Did you just realize that?
You are a real fool.
What do you want to be
if you were to be born again?
What about you?
I want to be...
I will be a tree.
A tree?
Yes, a tree.
Once it has taken root,
it can't move anywhere else.
I want to be such a tree.
Then I won't have to part with anyone
ever again.
So, we will say goodbye for now.
Eun Seo.
I will say goodbye to you now.
I will leave Mom, Dad, and you.
I told that to Mom already.
I told her I am not her daughter.
Eun Seo.
When you all leave me, I will be sad.
When you all leave for the U.S.,
I will be so sad.
So, I will forget about everything.
Please pretend we are strangers.
Pretend you don't know me, Jun Seo.
Can you do that for me?
Happy birthday, Eun Seo.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
This is for you.
Mom.
I love it.
Thank you, Mom.
- Happy birthday.
- Thanks.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
You are going to be late. Hurry up.
How many friends can I invite today?
As many as you want.
You can invite the whole class.
Are you sure?
By the way...
What about Eun Seo?
It is also Eun Seo's birthday today.
Yes, it is Eun Seo's birthday, too.
She is probably busy today.
Why would she be busy?
Would she come?
We have less than a week before we leave,
so it would be better
to have dinner together.
Is that okay with you?
What do you think, Sin Ae?
Yes.
Eun Seo.
How long are they going to
care about Eun Seo?
What?
This. Happy birthday.
Thanks, Jun Seo.
Thanks, it is a watch.
Does it look good? Thanks.
It is cute.
It looks expensive.
This.
You don't even wear this.
Can't I have it?
I gave this to Eun Seo
for her birthday last year.
So, you mean it belongs to Eun Seo?
Is that why you gave me this?
No. That watch is just your birthday gift.
Eun Seo wants to have this one.
Fine.
I understand.
It was Eun Seo's. So, give it back to her.
But I'll be the one to give it to her.
It is her birthday,
so this can be her birthday gift.
I have been wanting to make up
with Eun Seo before I leave.
Anyone who is available is welcome.
Of course, we are coming.
We are going to
have a party in our garden.
Then can we meet your brother?
Of course, you will.
It is his sister's birthday party.
If you want to come, anyone is welcome!
All right.
If you don't want to come,
I guess that is fine, too.
Are we going to have some food?
Of course, what kind of food do you want?
What I regret the most is that...
I left behind the watch
you had given me...
for my birthday last year, at home.
I can't wait to go.
I am really looking forward to it.
The blue wind blows
And creates a blue wave
In this green range
The bushes have grown a lot
The melted snow made valleys and creeks
Flowing down the land, and became a river
It's fine. Stop crying, Sin Ae.
Sin Ae, don't cry.
What is wrong with her?
Stop crying, Sin Ae. It is okay.
What is wrong? It's all right. Don't cry.
Don't cry.
Can I have your attention?
I am very disappointed right now.
I can't believe such a thing happened
in my class.
I am at a loss for words.
Everyone, place your bag on your desk.
And all of you,
get on your knees on the desk.
Yoon Sin Ae lost her watch.
Sin Ae, what does your watch look like?
It is a Mickey Mouse watch.
If anyone finds it...
please, bring it back to me.
It is so important to me.
Now, close your eyes.
Raise your hand if you have the watch.
I will let this go
if you turn yourself in now.
Nobody?
Okay, then you leave me with no choice.
Eun Seo, let me see your bag.
Eun Seo, what's wrong?
Choi Eun Seo.
Eun Seo.
No, I didn't do it.
I did not.
I can't believe this.
It is all right, teacher. I am fine.
Actually, I brought it to give to her.
So, it is all right.
No. I didn't.
I didn't do it.
It was under my desk. Jun Seo...
Jun Seo? Did he give it to you?
Did he?
(Teachers' Lounge)
Did Jun Seo give Eun Seo this watch?
Jun Seo saw me this morning...
putting the watch in my bag
to bring it to you.
Who is telling the truth?
Eun Seo,
you told me Jun Seo gave it to you.
Did you lie?
Yoon Jun Seo, tell the truth.
Did you give it to Eun Seo?
I...
No, he did not give it to me.
I have not even met him today.
Then, did you steal it?
Teacher, it is all my fault.
I should not have told you
I got it stolen.
If I had known she took it,
I would not tell you like that.
It was hers from the beginning.
It is my fault, teacher.
(I am a liar.)
Eun Seo, what have you done?
What happened?
Jun Seo.
Jun Seo, go with me.
Let's go together.
Many of my friends are coming to meet you.
Jun Seo, you should come home.
If you don't, you will regret it.
It is my party! Come on!
(I am a liar.)
(I am ashamed of being a liar.)
(I will not lie ever again.)
Eun Seo.
I said we should be strangers.
Okay, then.
Let's start from the beginning
as if we just met.
Hi, I am Yoon Jun Seo.
I hope we get along well.
By the way, you are so pretty.
I'm not a liar.
I didn't lie.
I didn't steal it. I swear.
I know that.
All right, if you do, I will be fine.
That is all that matters to me.
Let's go to the beach.
Okay.
I am done.
Who is this?
It's you.
Is it really me?
Am I this ugly?
- You don't like it?
- No, I don't.
Then, I will try something you would like.
Let's go.
I know you have been all alone.
Take mine with you.
You left with yours.
Please put mine and yours together.
Please do that.
Isn't it late?
We still have about half an hour
until the last bus.
Did you make a call home?
What do we do now?
Shall we make confessions,
which you like doing?
If there is anything
I did wrong to Eun Seo...
No, there is none.
Have I ever bullied you?
I have never hated or tricked you.
When are you leaving?
When are you leaving for the U.S.?
When are you coming back?
It will take a long time, right?
How long will it take?
I wonder how long it will take.
It'll probably take a long time, right?
How long might that be?
What if you forget about me?
What should I do if you forget about me?
What should I do, Jun Seo?
Eun Seo.
What do you want to be
if you were to be born again?
A tree.
I will remember that.
Even if I forget everything,
A tree.
- Kim Geum Sook.
- Yes.
- Jung Hye Jin.
Yoon Sin...
Yoon Sin Ae transferred today.
Sin Ae will study abroad in the U.S.
So, we need to vote
for a new vice president.
To replace Sin Ae...
Eun Seo.
Mom. Dad.
Jun Seo.
In the field where autumn wind has passed
Evening smoke rises up in thick clouds
Changing into colored clothes
Why did you stop?
Did you forget the lyrics?
Sing it again, come on.
Come on.
If you don't sing it now,
I won't see you again.
I won't hang out with you.
I won't even call you "brother."
So, sing it now.
Excuse me.
- Hello.
Can I lend a bike for a while?
Sure, just bring it as it is, please.
Okay, I will be back in a couple of hours.
Thank you.
You are my sister.
My sister.
(Hometown Restaurant)
Enjoy your meal.
Thanks.
You came here last year, right?
Yes, I did.
Did you find your sister?
No.
She has not come back here.
Rumor has it that
they could not stay in Seoul,
and moved to another place.
Her brother was a bad man.
Yes, I know that.
I will spend the night here,
and be back tomorrow early.
I thought you ran away
the day before your engagement party.
Did you go to your hometown
to meet your first love?
I can tell you that for sure.
You are wrong.
Have a good time.
I will be waiting for you.
I will be waiting for you right here.
Do you want me to take off more?
Just take off one more thing.
Then, how many are there?
One, two.
- Two.
Be quiet. Let me hear more.
What is it?
What did you do?
No. I need to hear more of it.
You said we are allowed to eavesdrop.
This is a telephone operator.
Ms. Choi, were you listening to all of it?
Who listened to what?
I said you could eavesdrop
when I am talking to a woman.
Was the talk too explicit?
I am going out to play golf.
I will put my laundry outside,
so please take care of that.
Please.
Can we have lunch tomorrow?
I'm just thankful.
I am not flirting with
a 37-year-old married woman.
No?
Are you that ugly?
Who is it?
His name is Tae Seok.
He is a professional golfer
staying in the villa for a long term.
How did you become
a 37-year-old married woman?
I am going home now.
Will you keep staying away from your job
even when you come here?
Just fire me, then.
That is not up to me.
You're Father's youngest and favorite son.
I think it is expensive.
Can you fire me for property damage?
Why is the ventilation system
not working in this room?
I am sorry, sir.
I will put you through
to the housekeeping department.
Hello.
Did you say the ventilation system
is not working?
I will let you know
how to operate it manually.
First, go to the bathroom.
Take the showerhead with your left hand,
and raise it over your head.
Can you see the button below?
Press the button.
It is cold.
Hey.
Why are you being rude?
I can tell you are younger.
How old are you?
I am 37 years old with two children.
Do you want to get hit?
Get out of the way.
You, there.
Get out of my way.
Hey.
Yoon Jun Seo.
Han Tae Seok. How have you been?
What made you come here?
I came to see you.
I guess you are being really patient.
I have to be. At least my father likes me.
It is fine except for my brothers visiting
to bother me from time to time.
No employees know about me.
It would be annoying if they knew
the CEO's son came here to get training.
Are you getting training?
I heard all you do is play golf.
That is my job.
Do you want to see my certificate?
I don't need to.
- Is this where you are staying?
- Yes, come on in.
Are you not working on art anymore?
He said I can do anything but art.
- Would you like a beer?
- Sure.
All right.
Aren't you getting bored
staying in a place like this alone?
I have Ms. Choi.
Who is Ms. Choi?
She is a very strict telephone operator.
I got along with her here.
You made me anxious.
I thought you were cheating on Sin Ae.
What do you think of me?
- How is Yu Mi?
- She is doing well.
Those were good times studying art
with you and Yu Mi.
When Sin Ae finishes school,
we will move to our hometown nearby.
Is Sin Ae coming, too?
I am not sure.
I will talk about it with dad and mom
tomorrow when I get back.
Are they here? I thought
they were coming back with Sin Ae.
Is there something wrong?
No.
I am getting engaged tomorrow.
What? You're finally getting engaged
to Shin Yu Mi?
Dude.
That is really nice.
Congratulations. Cheers.
Thanks.
What beautiful stars.
Fess up. What is it?
I wonder...
what made you come all the way here
when you are about to get engaged.
I have a secret girl.
A secret girl?
My family has a secret girl.
Just like my family.
My family has me, a secret son.
Who is she?
I came here to tell her I am engaged.
Did you tell her? What did she say?
Did I tell her?
I will, soon.
I will tell her.
I am getting engaged.
What about doing it this way?
You have your engagement party,
and I get to enjoy the first night.
What do you say? Isn't that a good idea?
Stop talking nonsense and just drive.
Jun Seo, do you remember?
When you first met me,
what was the first thing you asked me?
You asked what I wanted to be
if I were to be born again?
I remember that.
Do you also remember what I said?
Tree.
I'm taking root in you now, Jun Seo.
(Telephone Operators)
Yes, sir, yes.
- I will be back.
- Thank you.
Yes, this is the operator.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Is there a married woman here?
Here?
We are all in our early 20s.
Ms. Choi, please.
Hello, it's me.
I have something to tell you.
I do have something to tell you.
Hold on.
Just hear me out.
Did you meet your first love
in your hometown yesterday?
Hello?
Ms. Choi.
What was your first love like?
What is your real name?
What is the name of your first love?
Tree.
Eun Seo. Choi Eun Seo.
Take responsibility? How do I do that?
You can't get close to my room attendant.
Is it a woman?
How much are you worth?
I will buy you.
I will pay you more.
This beach...
This place is more than anything for me
with precious memories.
Will you be my girlfriend?
The number is 0215.
It is the same number as mine.
Whose birthday is it?
I meant your pager number.
It is my brother's birthday.
You must have returned without meeting
the person you were looking for.
I think I have been mistaken.
Because I missed her so much.